<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Some Useful Info</title><link>https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Some Useful Info</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 01:09:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adguard On OPNsense.</title><link>https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/adguardonopnsense/adguardonopnsense/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 01:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/adguardonopnsense/adguardonopnsense/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Adguard but with a twist.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>&amp;#x1f648; &amp;#x1f649; &amp;#x1f64a;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The &amp;quot;Notices&amp;quot; shortcode enables you to call out pieces of information - sidebars, warnings, tips, etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To create a notice on a page, you can use the &lt;code>notice&lt;/code> shortcode.&lt;br>
You use the &lt;code>notice&lt;/code> shortcode, with the first parameter being one of &lt;code>note&lt;/code>, &lt;code>info&lt;/code>, &lt;code>tip&lt;/code>, and &lt;code>warning&lt;/code>. Then add a title for your
note in quotes as the second parameter. The inner body of the note can be whatever markdown you want to create.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SpeedTestWidget</title><link>https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/speedtestwidget/speedtestwidget/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 21:48:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/speedtestwidget/speedtestwidget/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>My take on a speedtest widget for pfsense.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Being a newcomer to pfsense I guess i'm still playing catchup, as the newbie when my download speeds are nowhere near what i'm paying for I suspect pfsense as thats the only thing that changed in my setup.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Knowing what my broadband supplier is going to say I pre-empt this by doing my own diagnosis before calling them. I've disconnected everything from the back of my modem and plugged my laptop in directly, gone to &lt;a href="https://www.Speedtest.net">www.Speedtest.net&lt;/a> and hit the 'GO' button. Unfortunately the reading is no different (download speeds still suck).
One thing is for sure: I've just wasted several minutes dismantling a perfectly good hardware install, now I just have a mass of cables near my modem which need to be plugged back in.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rest Client in VS Code</title><link>https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/restclientinvscode/rest-client-in-vscode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 21:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Some-Useful.Info/posts/restclientinvscode/rest-client-in-vscode/</guid><description>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>A single application solution for when Postman is one application too many.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Due to the way Azure is delivered for the developer community at my place of work, all Internet facing systems need to be fronted by a Content Delivery Network.
To ensure this rule is followed a scan is carried out to find any Public IP's. Any public IP's found which did not follow any form of exception process are passed on to the security team, where a suitable enforcer is dispatched to help the guilty party remediate the situation.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>